Today we're making cookie rounds, a wonderful holiday treat.
Now that we have our wooden spoons and we've lightly oiled them, it's time to take our cookies and wrap them, or roll them rather, around our wooden spoons until they set and then put them on a wire rack.
While they're in there for a few seconds, go ahead and take another piece of wax paper and place it here.
This is where we'll work our cookies.
You'll also want your cooling rack.
Grab your cookies, grab your wooden spoon.
And you'll want to work, not right on the edge because the spoon gets too heavy so, but, where you can roll it.
So, grab a cookie and you can usually grab it without the spatula, if it sticks a little bit just go ahead and get your little metal spatula a loosen it again.
We're just going to get that in the picture.
We're just going to simply roll the cookie around the spoon.
And then set it aside for just a few seconds to let it take to that shape.
And that's why you want two or three of these so you don't have to wait around.
And again, flop it over and simply roll, and its ok, you're going to get chocolate over the paper, that's why I did that, and there's no real good way to do that.
Now this one's already starting to crack and harden around the edges so we may have to put these cookies back in the oven for a few more seconds.
Back in the oven for a few seconds.
This is the one we just did.
We'll take the spoon out, go get our cookies, and there we have it.
Let those cool and we'll arrange them nicely.
Share these with a friend and a cup of hot coffee.